export const AccordionData = [
  {
    question: "What is GreenSage Connect?",
    answer: `Greensage Connect is a cutting-edge mobile application designed to automate greenhouse and water irrigation systems. It simplifies the management of agricultural operations by providing real-time monitoring and control directly from your smartphone or tablet. With features like temperature and humidity monitoring, soil moisture level tracking, and advanced automation capabilities, Greensage Connect empowers farmers to optimize plant growth, conserve water, and maximize yields with ease and precision.`,
  },
  {
    question: "How does GreenSage Connect work?",
    answer: `Greensage Connect operates both remotely and locally, employing MQTT for remote communication and WiFi/WebSocket for local control. It utilizes the ESP32 microcontroller as its central processing unit.

Remote Operation: Through MQTT, vital environmental data collected by sensors within the greenhouse and irrigation systems is securely transmitted to the Greensage Connect mobile app. Users can monitor and manage their setup in real-time from anywhere.

Local Control: Greensage Connect also functions locally over WiFi and WebSocket protocols. This allows for seamless communication between the ESP32 controller and the mobile app within the local network, ensuring rapid response times and reliable control.

By leveraging MQTT and local network protocols, Greensage Connect provides a flexible, efficient, and user-friendly solution for optimizing greenhouse and irrigation systems.`,
  },
  {
    question: "Is the app propietary?",
    answer: `No, the app is open source and can be found on GitHub. But it copylefted`,
  },
  {
    question: "Can it work on IOS?",
    answer: `Yes, the app is available on both Android and iOS devices.`,
  },
  {
    question: "Where can the app be downloaded from?",
    answer: `The app can be downloaded from the Google Play Store and Apple App Store.`,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the cost of the app?",
    answer: `The app is free to download and use.`,
  },
  {
    question: "What are the system requirements for the app?",
    answer: `The app requires a smartphone or tablet running Android 5.0 or higher, or iOS 10.0 or higher.`,
  },
  {
    question: "What are the hardware requirements for the app?",
    answer: `The app requires an ESP32 microcontroller and various sensors to monitor and control greenhouse and irrigation systems.`,
  },
  {
    question: "How can I get technical support for the app?",
    answer: `For technical support, please contact us at pemtshewang500@gmail.com`,
  },
  {
    question: "Is the app available in multiple languages?",
    answer: `No, the app is currently only available in English.`,
  },
  {
    question: "How can I register for greensage connect to use MQTT features",
    answer: `To register for Greensage Connect, please visit our website and create an account (Eligible if you provide valid Bhutanese citizen ID.`,
  },
  {
    question: "Is the app available outside Bhutan?",
    answer: `Yes, the app is available for download and use worldwide. Buth the MQTT features are only available in Bhutan.`,
  },
  {
    question: "What are the plan for the future of the app?",
    answer: `We are constantly working to improve and expand the app's features. Our future plans include adding support for additional languages, enhancing automation capabilities, and integrating with more types of sensors and devices.`,
  },
];
